-= CHD字幕组 原创翻译 =-
字幕仅供翻译学习交流 谢绝用于任何商业用途
翻译：dengpao
校对：dahongying
片名：仇敌当前
对不起 伙计 我们不是故意要吓你
Sorry, dude. We didn't mean to sneak up on you.
只是找不到目的地了
It's just that we can't get to where we want to go.
你想要去哪儿？
Oh, where do you want to go?
我们正在找“帕克的历史足迹”
We're looking for Pike's Trail.
- “帕克的历史足迹”？  - 是啊
- Pike's Trail? - Yeah.
这张码头派发的地图我们搞不清楚
This map we got at the dock is no good.
是啊
Yeah.
那么 北在上 可能对你们有帮助
Well, north is up. That might help.
你们应该沿着海岸线找
And you might wanna think about staying close to the shoreline here.
万一迷路了山里没有手机信号
There's no cell reception in case you get lost.
往前走三刻钟
Just head up the trail about three clicks,
你会看到一棵大橡树 左转
you'll see a big oak tree, hook left.
再走10分钟不到…就是庐山真面目了
About another half click and... it should be right in front of you.
- 谢谢  - 谢谢你
- Thanks. - Thank you.
此外国王岛的规矩是
Also, hey, a couple house rules here on Kings Island.
不要在夜里乱走 不要扔垃圾还有…
You gotta go by dark, don't leave any trash and...
不要喝酒
no drinking.
好吧
Okay.
那么…扔掉啤酒
So... unload the beer.
得了 伙计
Come on, dude.
- 祝你愉快  - 再见
- Have a nice day. - Bye.
顺便说一下  别让人看到空瓶
By the way, don't let anyone see that flask.
今天怎么样？好吗？
How's your day going? Okay?
这条河水流向湖里
You know, this is the river that leads down to the lake.
我们必须把这…
We had to put this...
这里是所有岛中最大的一个
that we have of the island. It's the biggest one,
还列了很多注意事项
but there's also a list of things on here.
这里没有手机信号
Oh, there's no cell service up here.
希望你们还是多看看湖景吧
I'm afraid you'll just have to look at the lake.
桑德森先生 你在家吗？
Hey, Mister Sanderson. Are you home?
我知道你应该在的…
I actually know that you're around...
你家的烟囱在冒烟
'cause I saw the smoke coming outta the chimney.
你在煮东西？
Are you cooking something?
好像是炖肉？闻起来真香
Are you cooking like a stew? It smells really good.
一锅很棒的炖肉
It smells like good stew.
你不想邀请我吗？
You wanna invite me in for some?
走开 我没事
Go away. I'm fine.
我知道 我只是在做我的工作
I know, I know. I'm just doing my job.
你是唯一住在这岛上的人
You're the only other guy who lives on this island.
如果我不照顾我的邻居那会让人怎么看？
What would people think of me if I didn't check in on my neighbor?
"我没事" 听不懂吗？
Exactly what part of "I'm fine" don't you understand?
我…
I...
谢谢你对我的照顾 亨利
Thanks for checking in on me, Henry.
没问题 桑德森先生
Hey, no problem, Mister Sanderson.
不进来吃饭吗？不勉强了
Wanna come in for dinner? Oh, wouldn't wanna impose.
半径太大
The radius is too big.
妈的 我们应该在这些家伙起飞前就打落之
Shit, we should've hit these guys before take-off.
因为芝麻太小
Little thing called probable cause.
我们拿它没有办法 要命的制度
We didn't have it, fucking Constitution.
我们只能多招一些人
We could also use some more men.
是的 我们可以多招一些人
Yeah, we could use a lot of things.
这里边境线足有4000英里
We got four thousand miles of border here.
唯一的问题是 我们得仰仗加拿大
Only problem is we're looking at Canada.
加拿大方面不希望有人在这里偷渡
Canadians don't wanna sneak in here.
因此我们不得不仰人鼻息
That's why we don't get squat.
大家都只关心墨西哥偷渡
All anyone cares about is Mexicans sneaking in,
我们还是走到哪算哪吧
and we just happen to be facing the wrong fucking way.
赶紧挂了电话
Hang up. Now.
GPS有什么显示？
Where are we with the GPS modulator?
- 还没有精确定位  - 边境巡逻如何？
- Uh, nothing pinpointed yet. - What about border patrol?
飞机飞得太低 无法跟踪
Plane was flying too low for them to track it.
关闭飞机异频雷达收发机的原因只有一条
There's only one reason a plane flies without a transponder...
可以低飞避开雷达
and low enough to avoid radar,
必然是他们携带了一些见不得人的东西
and that's because they're carrying a load of some very naughty shit.
我们得警告湖边的年轻人
We're gonna have to troll the waterways, boys and girls,
可能要花上一通宵
and that could take all night.
开门
Open it.
请原谅我们的冒失
Pardon our intrusion.
我们是加拿大皇家骑警 正在巡逻
We are with the RCMP, patrolling the area.
听说你们需要帮助…
We heard you needed help...
找到沉入水底的可疑毒品
in locating a suspected drug delivery that went down
就是几个小时前发生在边境那边的
couple of hours ago along the border.
我们很熟悉本岛..
We have knowledge of the island...
愿提供我们的援助
and would like to offer you our assistance.
你们有点超出管辖范围了吧？
You're a bit out of your jurisdiction, aren't you?
还有 我们不使用马
And, uh, we don't use horses.
我们驾驶汽车
See, we drive cars.
约翰逊的意思是感谢
What Mister Johnson meant to say is thanks,
但多谢好意
but no thanks.
冠冕堂皇的骑警
Shitload of red-tape to team up with the Mounties.
非常多谢 我们会及时与你们联系的
Much obliged. We'll keep you posted.
请原谅  但我们真的可以帮助你们
Pardon me, but we can be really helpful.
我们有高压射灯
We have HMI lights,
我们有发电机和拖网工具
we have generator, we have trolling gear.
如果我们没在毒贩之前发现毒品
If we don't find the drugs before the runners,
毒品会被打捞运走
it will be picked up, shipped out,
明早就会一干二净
and chopped down by morning.
时间就是金钱
Time is of, uh, the essence.
我很感感激你们的好意 但心领了
I appreciate your concern, but not interested.
这次没有可合作的地方
There's no leads that we can share at this time.
头好晕
Well, giddy up.
搞什么法国佬？
Hey, what the fuck, Frenchie?
我告诉过你的人 我们不需要任何帮助
I told your boys we didn't need any help.
这算是某种玩笑？
Is this some sort of joke?
我看起来可笑吗？
Do I look funny to you?
是的 因为事实如此
Uh, yeah, as a matter of fact, you do.
因为我的鞋吗？
Is it my shoes?
也许吧
Uh, kinda.
我不穿皮革
You see, I don't wear leather.
我是素食主义者 保护环境人人有责
I'm a vegan. It's for the environment. I'm helping the planet.
那个啥 牛屁…
Do you know that cow farts...
占世界甲烷污染的四分之一？
are responsible for one quarter of the methane pollution in the world?
不许动！
Freeze!
放下枪
Drop the gun.
- 开枪打死他！  - 我不能出手！
- Shoot him! - I can't get a shot!
- 有两种选择  - 我是拿枪的人！
- We can do this one of two ways. - I'm the guy with the gun!
而我是拿人质的人
And I'm the guy with the guy.
不如你在GPS屏幕上指给我看飞机坠毁地点
You can turn over the GPS location of the crash,
我会让你死的不那么痛苦
and I spare you a painful death.
或者我们可以继续玩游戏
Or we can keep on playing games.
找到了
I have it.
很好 距离多远？
Good. How close?
在湖中间 距离岸边几公里
Middle of the lake, few kilometers from shore.
没有水深读数 但乘船可达
No read on depth, but easily reachable by boat.
- 你确定？  - 是的
- You're sure? - Yes.
希望沉底的包裹足够的牢靠
Let's hope it's wrapped tight.
它不是用来呆在水下的
It was not supposed to be under water.
我们走 可能还有护林员
Let's move. We'll find out about the ranger.
不能让任何人知道
We won't have any unknowns.
把马骑到码头去
Get the horses en route to the dock.
还有4小时才到轮岗时间
Four hours before replacements show up.
最好开悍马 那样更快
Better get the Humvee, it will be faster.
想想碳污染
Think about our carbon footprint.
想想下一代
Think about the children.
喂？有人吗？
Hello? Is anybody here?
喂？
Hello?
下面
Down here.
谢天谢地 我在这里已经几小时了
Thank goodness. I have been here hours.
我厌倦了喊救命的
I got tired of yelling for help.
你能下来吗？ 我卡住了
Could you come down here, please? I'm, I'm kind of stuck.
坚持  我马上就到
Yeah, hold on. I'll be right there.
- 你好  - 嗨
- Hi there. - Hi.
你完美的困住了自己
So you got yourself lodged in here pretty good?
是啊 真蠢
Yeah. It's, uh, it's kinda stupid.
我 我看到一个黑莓
I, um, I saw a blackberry.
你相信吗？
Can you believe that?
为找它我滑倒了扭伤了脚踝
Twisted my ankle reaching for it and I slipped.
然后就被卡在这里了
I'm, uh, I'm pinned in here.
好的 似乎并没有那么糟糕
All right. It doesn't seem so bad.
等一下 我们只需
Hold on, wait. Let's just, uh...
怎么样？怎么样你的腿？
How's that? How's the leg?
有点麻木
It's, uh, sore.
- 是吗？  - 是啊
- Is it? - Yeah.
把你抬上去 好吗？
Let's get you up on the path, okay?
- 哦  - 我托底
- Yeah. - Um, I'll stay here.
你转身我推你如何？ 你
Turn around and I'll push. All right? So you,
你只需… 我在下面托你
you just, uh, I'll stay back here and push you.
我看还是并排吧
Just, actually, let me get up next to you.
好吧
Okay.
- 准备好了吗？  - 是啊
- All right. Ready? - Yeah.
- 好 抱紧我  - 好的
- Okay. Just hold on to me. - Okay.
- 你可以自己站一下吗？  - 一小会儿
- Can you put any weight on it? - Some.
- 是吗？ - 是的
- Yeah?     - Yeah.
拿好 我抱你 好吗？
Here. I'm just gonna carry you, okay?
我就暂时忘记女权主义吧
I'm gonna lose my feminist card for this.
你不愿意我就不告诉其他人
Well, I won't tell anyone if you don't.
嘿 伙计们 手机信号塔倒下了…
Hey, guys, you know the cell tower is down and...
我的天啊！
Holy shit!
没有手机信号 无线电被捣毁
No cell, radio's busted.
国王岛水域有GPS信号
There's a GPS signal coming from the water near Kings Island.
这就是他们的目的地 他们要去码头！
That's where they're headed. They're going to the dock!
看起来并不太坏
It doesn't look too bad.
只需要保持抬高
We'll just keep it elevated.
我可以绑得更紧 会减少肿胀
I could tie it a little tighter. That would keep the swelling down.
- 好吧  - 好的 你准备好了吗？
- Okay. - Okay. You ready?
我会数到三
I'll pull on three.
一 二 三
One, two, three.
你骗我
You tricked me.
你是军人？
So, are you a military guy?
是啊 你怎么知道？
Yeah. How'd you know?
长得像呗
You got the look.
那里有你的照片
Also, you know, the photographs over there.
是的 我是一个潜水员
Uh, yeah, I was a diver.
也就是所谓的蛙人
Uh, they used to call us frogmen.
听起来有意思
Wow, that sounds exciting.
我的意思是这是高度危险的工作
Uh, well, I mean, I guess it depends on the level of danger.
我的意思是听上去不那么有意思
Right. I mean, I didn't mean it sounded fun.
这不是普通的朝九晚五
Just, you know, it's not your normal nine-to five.
你不会一直一个人在这里吧？
So, you never get lonely being out here, all by yourself?
每周末这里有几百号人
Couple hundred people come through here every weekend.
人群蜂拥而来
Yeah, but there's being around people,
然后就得面对大批人群
and then there's being with people.
我可能蠢话连篇？对不起
Could I be sounding more of a bitch? I'm sorry.
不 我理解的 看起来很怪咖
No, no, no. I understand. It must look pretty weird.
我只是 我只是需要一个人呆着
I just, uh, I just needed to be by myself, so...
六根清净而已
Had to clear my head of some stuff.
你在这里已经呆多久了？
Right, so how long you been here?
- 三年  - 三年？
- Three years. - Three years?
那应该彻底清净了吧
Well, it must be pretty clear by now.
清净很多了 但还有点阴暗面
Clear. It's getting better. Still a bit murky.
清净还是阴暗
Well, clear or murky, it's a,
至少这颗脑袋还不错
it's a nice head.
谢谢
Aw, thanks, ma'am.
脚踝感觉如何？
Hey, um, how's the ankle feeling?
好多了
Better.
很好 因为天马上就要黑了
Good, 'cause it's gonna get dark soon.
水面航行忌讳没有光亮
We don't wanna lose the light on the water.
上独木舟吧
Probably could get you down to your canoe.
- 好吧  - 准备好了？
- Okay. - Ready?
- 是啊  - 嘿 你知道…
- Yeah. - Hey, you... know,
独木舟用做快速班船是没有问题的
it would be no problem to quickly shuttle you across the water.
太好了 但我会没事的
That's kind, but I'll be fine.
此外 我不想留下我的独木舟
Besides, I don't want to leave my canoe here.
好的
Okay.
我们应互留信息
We should exchange info, though.
以便你知道我安全返回了
So you know I made it back safely.
太好了
Oh, yeah. Yeah, that's great.
好吧
Okay.
我从你的办公室偷了一张地图
I, uh, I stole a map from your office.
我希望你不介意
I hope you don't mind.
这样的事情发生几千次了
Those things are worth like, thousands, you know.
那么用价值百元的纸片
Well, use this hundred dollars worth
记下你的电话号码
to write down your number.
我在晚餐前打电话给你
And I can call you before dinner.
晚餐？
Dinner?
是啊 晚饭
Yeah. Dinner.
一起吃晚饭
You know, eating a meal at night together.
耳鬓厮磨 增进彼此了解
Speaking in between bites to get to know someone.
下周的某个时候？
Uh-huh. Um, next week sometime?
我在想最好是今晚
I was thinking more like tonight.
我的地址在后面
My address is on the back.
我会等到你九点？
I'll expect you around nine?
在星空下吃野餐？
We could eat a picnic under the stars?
因为你今天救了我 让我说声谢谢
You saved me today. Let me say thank you. Please.
我不知道
I don't know.
我小屋里面还有很多活要干
I've got a lot of stuff to do up at the lodge.
是的 我注意到了 有意义的活动
Yeah, I noticed. It's a, a real hub of activity.
让我感激你一下嘛
Come on. I'm so grateful to you.
晚餐而已 今晚见
It's dinner, for God's sake. I will see you tonight.
- 我在那里等你  - 再见
- I'll see you there. - Bye.
小…
Eeny...
微小 迷你 …
meeny, miny...
干
moe.
去拿装备
Get the equipment.
5分钟内离开
We're leaving in five.
投篮 得分！
He shoots, he scores!
来了
Coming.
感谢上帝！我还以为没人在家
Oh, thank God! I was starting to think nobody was home.
这么晚你在岛上做什么？
I'm here. What are you doing on the island so late?
我的船停在岛的另一侧
Oh, I, I beached my boat like, way on the other side of the island.
登山之后我迷路了
I just started hiking, and I got lost.
太阳落山了 我找不到回去的路
Sun went down, I couldn't find my way back to the trail.
你是唯一数英里内我能看到亮光的地方
Yours was the only light I saw for miles.
很高兴你找到了我 进来吧 让你暖和一下
Glad you found me. Come on in. Get you warmed up.
- 抱歉一团糟  - 对
- Sorry about the mess. - Right.
有什么需要？
Can I get you anything?
- 一杯水最好不过了  - 好吧 在后边
- A water'd be great. - All right, come on right back here.
这里没有很多的居民 是不是？
Not a lot of residents around here, I take it?
对 只有我 还有另外一个家伙
No, it's just me. There's another guy,
他有个祖传屋子在这里
had his cabin grand-fathered in
在被宣布为国家公园之前
before they declared this a state park.
我觉得自己像个白痴一样迷路
I feel like an idiot getting lost like I did.
不要 国王岛不容易向导的
Don't be. Kings Island, it's not easy to navigate.
所以我们必须在太阳落山前搞定一切
It's why we got all the signs saying leave before the sun hits the horizon.
- 感谢您  - 没问题
- Thanks for that. - Sure.
我们接下来怎么办 先生…？
So what are we gonna do with you, Mister...?
克雷 大家都叫我克雷
Clay. Everybody call me Clay.
我猜你不得不在这过夜
I guess you're gonna have to spend the night,
如果你不介意睡在地板上
if you don't mind sleeping on the floor.
我有额外的毯子和枕头
I've got extra blankets and a pillow.
明早再去找你的船
And in the morning, we'll look for your boat.
好的
Cool.
你在附近还是城里工作？
So you work up near here or down in the city?
现在没有工作
Not working at all right now.
原来是建筑工人 但现在变成这样…
Was a construction worker but that turns into day...
一旦停止建筑工程 劳力就失业
laborer pretty quick when people stop building.
是的 我听说了
Yeah, I hear that.
工业化似乎把人们拒之门外了
Though the economy seems to bring people to the outdoors.
我们这里一直很忙碌
We've been pretty busy up here.
一线希望 可以这么说？
Silver lining, so to speak?
那么这工作是怎么一回事？
So is that what this job is all about?
与大自然亲密接触？
Getting in touch with nature?
可以这么说
So to speak.
我想你会说我到这里是出于某些目的
I guess you could say I came up here for a little bit of perspective,
很难解释
but it's hard to explain.
嗯 我去拿毯子和枕头
Well, I'll get the blankets and the pillow.
实际上我今晚出去 不会很晚回来
I'm actually going out tonight and I won't be back until late.
要出去吗？这么晚了？
Going out? This late at night?
看起来你像拿一把刀和一把枪对打
Looks like you brought a knife to a gun fight.
亨利 你还挺有警觉性
I've gotta give it to you, Henry, you're kinda perceptive.
肯定的 叫什么来着 军事训练
Must be that, what you call, military training.
打马虎眼 借以靠近敌人 坐下
Duck and cover, enemy approaching. Sit.
如果你想要钱  我没有
If you want money, I don't have any.
我要钱的话
If that was what I was after,
你以为我会来这种地方？
you think I'd come to a place like this?
难道这里是金矿 对不？
It's a fucking gold mine, right?
你想干什么？
What do you want?
与我想要的无关 事关正确的事
It's not about what I want, it's about what's right.
事关正确的事
It's about what's just.
不管你觉得我刚才做了什么
Whatever you think I did,
我可以向你保证 我不是那个意思
I can assure you I didn't do it.
这就是你错误的地方 亨利
See, that's where you're wrong, Henry.
你什么都保证不了
You can't assure nobody of nothing.
我会永远把任务放在第一位
I will always place the mission first.
我永远不会接受失败
I will never accept defeat.
我绝不放任战友倒下
I will never leave a fallen comrade behind.
听起来很熟悉？
That sound familiar?
我说了你就会明白
I'm telling you this so you'll understand.
我一直都知道我会像我爹一样一无所成
I always knew I was gonna be a fuck-up like my old man.
但我不绝望
And I did not disappoint.
不 先生 所以我必须确保我弟弟与众不同
No, sir. So I had to make sure my baby brother was the opposite.
在学校里 他得到了B 我给他一皮带
In school, he get a "B" I'd belt him one,
确保他得到A
make sure he raised it to an "A."
他成就了我没有成就的一切
He was everything I wasn't.
他就是一个全能明星
He was a fucking all-star at everything.
他应征入伍 以取得大学资格
He enlisted so he could go to college.
我告诉他  如果你要去当兵
And I told him, if you're gonna be a soldier,
就得当个排头兵
you're gonna be the best soldier.
我在身后推动他…
I pushed him...
我真希望也有人推动我
the way I wish somebody had pushed me.
他当上了特种部队
When he made Special Forces,
这是我的生活中最值得骄傲的一天
it was the proudest day in my life.
几个月后
Few months later,
我被关起来了 因为这狗屁的指控
I got locked up for this bullshit assault charge.
我收到信…
That's where I got the letter...
说我德克尔被打死…
telling me Decker'd been killed...
- 在阿富汗交火中  - 德克尔！
- in a firefight in Afghanistan. - Decker!
- 你是德克尔的哥哥  - 我说闭嘴！
- You're Decker's brother. - I said shut the fuck up!
我真是有苦说不出
Now that's a hard pill to swallow,
发现弟弟被杀
finding out your baby brother's been killed.
但是无论如何…
But what made it even harder...
我发现他是被遗弃了
was learning he had been abandoned
被他的指挥官遗弃
by his commanding officer
死在敌人手中
and left to die at enemy hands.
他们派遣我们的时候不知道会有风险
They sent us in, without knowing the risks.
这不是我的错
It wasn't my fault.
这不是任何人的错
It wasn't anyone's fault.
那么你为什么要辞职？
So why did you resign?
军事决策失误
The military acted on bad Intel.
上头的指令不可理由
They gave the order, it went crazy.
我不知道我…
I don't know I...
我想我不能再承受
I guess I just couldn't take it any more.
他妈的扯淡！
That is fucking bullshit!
承认吧 承认你使我弟弟被杀害
Admit it. Admit you got my brother killed.
现在承认
Confess it right now,
我保证你死得痛快
and I will make sure your death is quick.
你一直在骗我
But you keep lying to me,
我答应你个痛快
and I promise you, it will be anything but.
他们命令我们进入风暴地带
They ordered us into a shitstorm,
你弟弟走散了
your brother got separated,
如果我们都进去的话 所有人都得死
and if we'd have gone in there, we'd have all been shredded.
我必须保护我的部下
I had to protect my team.
你保护的是自己！
You had to protect yourself!
他妈的懦夫
You're a fucking coward.
你应该身先士卒 亨利
You should've been leading the charge, Henry,
不应该躲在后面
not falling behind it.
亨利 我是凯拉
Hey, Henry, it's Kayla.
我只是想告诉你 我迟到几分钟
Um, I just wanted to tell you that I'm running a few minutes late,
但是我…
but I...
你没必要这么做
You don't have to do this.
我们有解决办法的
We can work this out.
不 我们没有
No, we can't.
伙计们
Oh, you guys.
真好 纯净清新的空气
Now that is good, pure, crisp air.
埃托 准备好潜水了？
Eto, are you ready to dive?
差不多
Just about.
- 弗朗索瓦  - 我们正在接近
- Francois. - We're getting close.
时刻表如何？
And how are we for time?
轮岗到达还有三个小时二十分
The next shift arrives in three hours, twenty minutes.
清楚了
We are clear till then.
派两人下去
I want to be gone in two.
我们将得到50磅 纯的
We have to retrieve fifty pounds of pure,
白色完整无缺的海洛因
white, uncut heroin,
一磅又一磅
and pound for pound,
它的价值超过你们每一个人
it's worth more than each of you.
你们要表现的物有所值
So make yourselves worth a lot.
醒了？
You awake? Huh?
You awake?
起来了 我拖累了你的屁股
Get up. I'm tired of carrying your ass.
我说起来了！
I said get up!
你曾有机会的 不是吗？
You had me there for a second, didn't you?
还好我有准备
Good thing I over-prepared.
没什么能阻止这一天的到来
Nothing could have stopped this day.
听到了吗？
You hear me?
这事情结束了你不会感觉更好的
You won't feel better when it's over.
也许吧  停下来
I might. Stop.
拿着
Take this.
干什么？
What are you doing?
枪膛里有子弹
It's got a bullet in the chamber.
抵在头上 扣动扳机
You put it to your head, you pull the trigger.
做光荣的事情
Do the honorable thing.
你在监狱学到的的光荣？
Did you learn about honor in prison?
也许吧  我那时时间很多
Maybe I did. I did my time.
现在是你赎罪的时候了
Now it's time for you to pay for your sins.
来吧
Go ahead.
抵在头上 扣动扳机
Put it to your head and pull the trigger,
如果你不够男人做到这一点
'cause if you're not man enough to do it,
我答应你 我会的
I promise you, I will.
很长以来我一直想这样做
You know, for a long time I wanted to do this.
该死的每天
Every goddamn day.
你以为我没责怪自己吗？
You think I didn't blame myself? Do you?
我不能派更多的人进去
I couldn't send any more men in.
他也不会允许这种情况发生
He wouldn't have let that happen,
没有哪个人会
no soldier would,
他是一名军人
And he was a soldier.
我觉得我可以做得更好
I still think I could have done more,
只是我不知道怎么去做
except I don't know what the more is.
我失去了工作 买醉
I lost my career, I drank.
我有一个儿子
I have a son.
自从我妻子离开以后我还没有见过他
I haven't seen him since my wife threw me out.
所以我就尽量远离一切
So I got as far away from everything
因为我可以一个人在这里
as I could and here I am.
有那么一段时间 我感觉就像我杀了他
After a while, I stopped feeling like I killed him.
有那么一段时间
A little bit at a time.
我觉得你来晚了
So I guess you're just too late.
前一阵子 我会很乐意这样做
A while ago I would have done it gladly.
现在你得亲自来干
Now, you're just gonna have to do it yourself.
抱歉
Sorry.
好吧
Very well then.
不要说话
Don't you say a word.
我们是移民与海关执法局
This is Immigration and Customs Enforcement.
他们不是警察 警察一般没有夜间巡逻
That's not ICE. They don't patrol at night.
- 至少在没有与我联系  - 你们
- At least not without contacting me. - You there.
- 让我看你的手  - 当然 是我不好 我们只是
- Let me see your hands. - Sure, my bad. We just, uh,
在这里夜钓鳟鱼
out here night fishing. Trout.
离开海滩 现在
You need to leave the beach. Now.
没问题 我们一夜什么也没有打到
No problem. We ain't caught nothing all night anyway.
- 谁和你在那儿？  - 我是护林员
- Who's there with you? - I'm the park ranger.
这是怎么回事？
What's going on here?
只是抓住了他 他说是夜钓的
Just caught him night fishing like he said.
看起来倒像是他抓了你
Looks like he caught you.
先生们 站好了？
Gentlemen, mind stepping forward?
趴下！
Get down!
是枪声？
Was that gunfire?
这可不是"生逢七月四"
Well, it ain't the fourth of July.
埃托  下来
Eto's down.
妈的
Shit.
他妈的
Fuck.
不
No.
糟糕
Eh. Shit happens.
埃托
Eto.
闭上眼睛
Close your eyes.
这到底怎么回事？
What the hell was that?
用猎枪的家伙是谁
Who was that guy with the shotgun,
为什么护林员在那里？
and why was the ranger there?
我还以为搞定他了
I thought he was accounted for.
我哪知道 他身上又没有标签
I don't know. We had tabs on him.
你怎么可能不知道？
How do you not know?
你不知道你距离死亡有多近
Oh. You don't know how close you came.
我们上岸
So, let's get to the landing strip.
我们不知道枪声是否被人听见了
We don't know if anyone heard those shots.
没有人住在这里 除了护林员
No one lives here except the ranger.
我们可以利用他
We can work with this.
我们利用护林员完成任务
We complete the mission with the ranger.
他有训练 会潜水
He has training, he can make the dive.
找到护林员 杀死另外的家伙
We hunt the ranger. We kill the other guy.
不要错误 不要犹豫
No mistake. No hesitation.
走
Let's go.
有打斗痕迹
Signs of struggle.
座机破损
The phone is shattered.
肯定是我们的新朋友
That must be our new friend.
弄沉所有的船
Sink all the canoes.
保证这地方除了我们没有人能离开
No one gets off of this place except us.
外面有条船
There is a boat tied up outside.
发动机还是热的
The engine's still warm.
弄沉它
Sink it.
没人允许你离开！
No one asked you to leave!
把皮艇放下来
Put the kayak down.
现在开始走
Now start walking.
无论你们干什么 只管做
Whatever you guys are up to, go ahead and do it.
只是别在我的公园乱抛垃圾
Just don't litter my park.
幽默的护林员？很搞笑
Oh, park ranger humor? Very funny.
另外的人在哪？
Where is the other guy?
我不知道 我也不想知道
I don't know and I don't wanna know.
他带我到这里的 用枪指着我
You know, he led me down here at gunpoint.
他想杀了我
He wanted to kill me.
那我们杀了他你一定不会难过
Well then, you won't be sorry when we kill him.
我不希望你死？他们希望
I don't want you dead, okay? They do.
接下来的几个小时 我们得合作…
In the next few hours, we're gonna have to work together...
如果我们想要生存下去
if we wanna survive.
合作？
Work together?
你疯了吧？
Have you lost your goddamned mind?
听着 服役的时候
Listen, in the service,
我们被称为巴基斯坦“特种部队”
they paired us up with Pakistani "special forces".
那些无能的混蛋想要我们死
These incompetent assholes who wanted us dead.
尽管不喜欢他们 但是我们得合作…
And we didn't like them either, but we worked together...
在某些时候
knowing that at some point,
或是将来的某一天…
either later that same day...
或者从现在起20年政局改变之后
or twenty years from now when the politics changed,
我们才会杀死对方
we'd be trying to kill each other again.
你明白我在说什么？
You understand what I'm saying?
走
Let's go.
吉恩？吉恩 报告
Jean? Jean, report.
索尔 我们已经失去吉恩
Saul, we've lost Jean.
估计有难度
Be prepared for heavy resistance.
明白 我们…在游客中心的时候 我拿了一张地图
Understood. When we were... in the visitors center, I took a map.
我现在在看
I'm looking at it now,
它标出了另一小屋…在内陆
and it shows another cabin... further inland.
拿好地图 我来了
Take care of it. I'm on my way.
他们到底是什么人？
So, who the fuck are they?
受过军事训练 听起来像是法裔加拿大人
Military trained. French Canadian by the sound of it.
可能是雇佣军 或毒贩…
Probably mercenaries, either working the drug routes...
或检漏者
or picking off the leftovers.
都有可能
A lot of drama for some weed.
他们武器很好
They got too much firepower.
意思是这次油水很足咯
It's gotta be something more lucrative.
是的 确有道理
Okay, makes sense.
下一步怎么办？
So what's our next move?
去寻求帮助
We gotta call for help.
你毁了我的电话
You destroyed my phone,
我们需要另外一部电话 有个老头…
so we need another one and there's an old man...
就在距离此处几英里的地方
lives a few miles up this way.
我们现在直奔过去
That's where we're headed.
停下来
Stop.
你确定他有电话吗？
You sure he's got a phone?
我不知道 但他是我们唯一的选择
I don't know. But he's our only option.
看不到人…巡逻范围内
No visual... on the park ranger,
地面有具尸体
but, uh, there's a body on the ground.
应该是吉恩
I think it's Jean.
呆在原地 尽量别通讯
Yes, stay on the trail. Minimal comms.
保持无线电静默
Radio compromised.
好的
I guess that's that.
他已经知道了 这家伙很聪明
He already knew. This guy's pretty smart.
怎么？
What?
你弟弟知道他在做什么
Your brother knew what he was doing,
他不会让我们为他作无畏的牺牲
and he never would've let us sacrifice ourselves for him.
现在是非常时刻
If this little truce of ours is gonna hold,
现在不谈我弟弟 懂吗？
let's not talk about my brother right now, okay?
我只是觉得你应该知道整个事情的经过
I just think you should know the whole story
在杀一个人之前
before you kill a person.
换作我是你
If I were you,
我绝不会和拿枪的人谈我的兄弟
I wouldn't talk to me about my brother while I'm holding a gun.
有见地
Good point.
走
Let's go.
妈的！
Shit!
你听到了吗？
Did you hear that?
听到什么？
Hear what?
既然你在问 说明你没听到
If you have to ask, then you didn't hear it.
野生草莓
Fragaria x ananassa.
The wild strawberry.
我不知道你居然能在这种环境里长成
I wasn't aware you grew in these parts.
他们一英里外都会闻到的
They'll smell that a mile away.
你怎么知道是我？
So how'd you know about me?
你的纹身 还有凭直觉
Your tattoo. And just intuition, really.
你身上有股杀人的气息
You get a feel for someone who wants you dead.
时间？
Time?
两个半小时
Two and a half hours.
先生们…晚上好
Gentlemen... good evening.
不管手持对讲机的人是谁 我想谈谈
I would like to speak to whoever has the walkie.
我们时间有限
We are under time constraints.
必须完成工作
We want to finish our work.
如果现在就结束 则没有人会受伤
End this now and no one else gets hurt.
对方走了错误的一步
That's the wrong move.
我们终于知道他们想要什么
We have a conversation, find out what they want.
现在我们知道了
We know what they want.
他们是毒贩 需要那些毒品
They're drug dealers. They want their drugs.
我直话直说 我只要护林员
Allow me to be direct. I simply want the park ranger.
另外的家伙 你可以走了
The other guy, you can go.
这并不意味着我会相信你
This don't mean I trust you.
走
Move.
如果改变主意 你知道怎么找到我
If you change your mind, you know how to reach me.
时刻恭候
I'm in the book.
还有多远？
How much further?
快了 应该很快就会看到
We're close. We should see it soon.
桑德森先生
Mister Sanderson.
- 撞开  - 不 闯入不好
- Break it down. - No, it's not a home invasion.
我不想做个入侵者
I don't want to involve the guy,
我只是想进去打个电话然后走人
I just wanna get in, make the call, and get out.
别管窗户
Forget the window.
不 这才是最佳机会
No, this is our best chance.
我们还是从门进
No, we go in this door.
没时间正人君子了
We don't have time for this.
我先进去 然后你进去
I'll go, then you go.
我进去以后就无处可逃了
I've got nowhere to run once I'm inside.
你走错一步的话 我就轰你一个洞
You make one wrong move, you're gonna have a new asshole.
听到了吗？
You hear me?
现在照我的方式做
Now we do this my way.
不是相互信任吗？
What happened to trust?
我信任你 你去打电话 拨号
I trust you to go pick up that phone and dial out.
- 怎么？  - 电话坏了
- What?     - It's dead.
- 给我  - 你以为我在说谎？
- Give it to me. - What, you think I'm lying?
妈的
Aw, shit.
你以为这里是哪里？
Just what do you think this is?
是想来就来的酒店？
A goddamn hotel?!
把枪放地上 箱子旁边
Put the gun down right there on the box.
- 桑德森先生…  - 照我的话做 孩子！
- Mister Sanderson... - Do as I say, boy!
快点
Hurry.
好的 好的
Okay, okay.
我还以为你认识他？
I thought you said you knew this guy?
是我 桑德森先生 是我 亨利
I do. Mister Sanderson, it's me, Henry.
你不认识我了？
Don't you recognize me?
我脑子没傻
I've not gone dumb up here.
你闯进我家
You broke into my house.
我有权利捍卫家园
I got a right to defend it.
我们不是来找你的 老头
Look, we ain't here for you, old man.
有一群毒贩在狩猎我们
We got drug dealers out there hunting us,
试图杀死我们
trying to kill us.
在我看来 像你们两个倒像是敌人
Seems to me like you two are trying to kill each other.
- 情况有点复杂  - 情况永远复杂
- Well, it's complicated. - Always is.
听着 我们只需要用您的电话
Listen, we just need to use your phone,
致电警方 然后离开这个岛…
call the authorities, and get off this island...
- 趁着我们还没死之前  - 电话坏了
- before anybody gets killed. - Phone don't work.
我几年前就割断了电话线
I had it cut off a couple of years back.
那你为什么还把电话机放在桌上？
Why the fuck is it sitting on the table then?
装饰装饰
It looks nice.
喂 这房子不错
Hello again. It's a nice house.
帮个忙 你可以把护林员交出来吗？
Do me a favor, can you please send me the park ranger?
他不在这里
He's not here.
我们现在得离开这里
We gotta get out of here. Now.
我哪里也不去
I ain't going nowhere.
桑德森先生 这与你无关
Mister Sanderson, this has nothing to do with you.
这些疯狗想要咬人 我喂他们个饱！
These fellas want a bite. I'll give 'em a mouthful!
莫里斯 抄后路 不许有人出来
Morris, cover the back. Nobody gets out.
离开我的地盘！
Piss off my land!
这家伙还挺疯狂
This guy's kinda cranky.
里面的人 我讨厌枪
Hey, you people inside, I hate guns.
它们不利于环境
They are very bad for the environment.
当然 我也不傻
However, I'm not stupid.
先生们 帮帮忙
Gentlemen. A little help.
趴下！
Get down!
我经常遇到的徒步旅行者
I get hikers here from time to time,
想把我赶出我的家
trying to run me outta my home.
徒步者？你真以为外面的是徒步者？！
Hikers? You seriously think those are hikers?!
先生！我们得离开这间屋子
Sir! We gotta leave this house.
我们这是坐以待毙
We're sitting ducks here and you know it.
拿上
Take that.
难道我是透明的？为什么给他不给我？
What, am I invisible? Why him and not me?
我不认识你
I don't know you.
我知道外面那些是混蛋
I do know fellas like those assholes.
开枪打他们的脚
Couple shots around their feet,
他们就会猪叫着跑开
they'll run off like squealing pigs.
- 你会明白的  - 我不认为你懂…
- You'll see. - I don't think you understand...
当下的情势
the situation that we're in right now.
我们非常感谢您的帮助
We appreciate your help,
但最后一次
but for the last time, this doesn't seem...
把护林员交出来…
Give us the ranger...
我们就会走人
and we'll go away
明早你们就不记得这场噩梦
like a bad dream you won't remember in the morning.
伙计们 我不知道你们两个搞什么鬼
Fellas, I don't know what's gone on between the two of you.
你必须自己扛
You gotta get past it.
老话说 一条绳子上的蚂蚱
Old saying goes, Hang together, or hang separately.
刀子？他妈的我拿刀子有什么用？
A knife? What the fuck am I gonna do with a knife?
刀子可以做很多事情
Man can do a lot with a knife.
我非常信任你
That's how much I trust you.
现在只要保持低头
Now just stay low.
在我们被包围之前 你得安全回来
You're gonna have to fall back before they get us surrounded.
我没有问题
Fine by me.
不行 你和我们一起走
No. Not fine. You're coming with us.
我自有一套 你们先走
I've got my ways of getting through this. Just go.
你们先走 从后面走
You boys get outta here. Go out the back.
直奔东面 亨利你反正认路
Head east. Oh, hell, Henry, you know the route.
不！
No!
在我开枪之前 走
Go before I shoot you myself.
这不是商业谈判
This ain't a negotiation.
你还有余生可以做英雄
You got the rest of your life to be a hero.
我只有这最后的机会了
I just got this one time.
目前的窘境是我带来的
I brought this to you.
你留下 我也留下
You stay, I stay.
好… 那好吧
Well... okay then.
随便你们
I guess that settles it.
不！
No!
他死了
He is gone. He's gone.
我会很乐意你和他一起死
And I'll be happy to let you go with him,
但我需要你离开这个岛
but I need you to get off this island.
你是说有时候
You mean sometimes,
只能眼睁睁看着别人去死？
you have to leave a guy in trouble?
还有更多的弹药？
Do you have any more shells?
我没料到我会需要这么多
I didn't think I would need any.
真是好极了
Well, that's just perfect.
那老头刚才说
Like the old guy said,
“刀可以做很多事情”
"A man can do a lot with a knife."
他们走了
They're gone.
呼叫莫里斯
Morris, come in.
我被击中了 他们走了
I'm hit. They are gone.
- 你被打到哪里？  - 肩
- You're hit where? - Shoulder.
用另一部  你过来
Use the other one. Move your ass.
他们去哪儿了？
Hey. Where did they go?
亲我的老屁股！
Kiss my geriatric ass!
你确定吗？
Are you sure about that?
等等 等 等等！让他站起来
Wait, wait, wait, wait! Stand him up.
有机作物嘛 好男人
Organic. Good man.
我是小男孩的时候 在我祖母家
When I was a little boy at my grandmama's place,
她有一只可爱的鹅
she had a lovely goose.
我叫她伊迪丝
I named her Edith,
后来法国有个歌手叫伊迪丝・琵雅芙
after the French singer Edith Piaf.
我真的喜欢那只鹅
I truly loved that goose.
每个人都觉得好笑
Everybody thought it was funny.
后来有一天晚上吃饭的时候
Then one night when we were at dinner,
我祖母对我说 “伊迪丝味道也不错 不是吗？”
my grandmama said to me, "Edith tastes good, no?"
我从饭桌跑开
I ran out of that table,
我吐了 哭的像个孩子
I puke up, I cry like a child.
于是乎 我成了一个素食主义者
Ever since, I became a vegan.
为此 我必须杀了她
I'm telling you, I had to kill her.
没时间了 我需要潜水员
We're losing time. I need my diver.
我没耐心了…
My patience is losing weight...
不 不 正规用语应该是
No, no, that's why they say, they say,
我气炸了
I'm getting real pissed.
我们走
Let's go.
我们得到岛的另一边
We've gotta get to the other side of the island,
你停船的地方
where your boat is.
但我撒谎了
Yeah, I kind of lied about that.
我付钱请人带我来这里的
I paid a guy to bring me here.
他应该明早来接我
He's supposed to come back in the morning.
有B计划吗？
You got a plan B?
你在这里躲过夜  挨到明早
You hide till morning and make it through the night.
你要我躲起来？
And you want me to hide?
你自己怎么办？
What are you gonna do?
我引他们离开
I'm gonna lead them away from here.
他们只要跟着我们其中一人 就能抓住两个
Right now, they track one of us, they catch both of us.
我要和这疯子斗斗战
I'm gonna take the fight to this maniac.
- 用什么？  - 有什么用什么
- With what? - Whatever I got.
我们只有这些
All we got is this.
我有火柴
I got some matches,
一卷钓鱼线 一些绳子
a spool of fishing line and some rope.
这些东西能吓死人
Well, that'll scare the shit out of 'em.
我只为今晚做过准备
Look, man, I came prepared for one night.
我可不是来打仗的
I didn't come prepared for war.
这场战斗是自己找上门来的
Yeah, well, this war came to us.
如果这次我们都活下来 我们再坐谈 好吗？
Listen, if we both survive this, let's talk, okay?
你弟弟是个好战士
Your brother was a wonderful soldier.
他是天生的特种部队
He had to be in Special Forces.
一直是冲锋陷阵的第一人
Always had to be the first man through the door.
我一直奇怪他被什么样的力量驱动着？
I wonder what or who made him that way, huh?
你一直推动他 请你也考虑考虑
Always pushing. Maybe you think about that, too.
你最好扪心自问一下
I'll bet you do.
没有哪一天不曾想过进入风暴的应是我而不是他
Not a day goes by I don't wish it wasn't me instead of him.
一天都没有停过
Not a day.
这把刀我需要
I'm gonna be needing this.
先生们 我长话短说
Gentlemen, I'll put it simply.
亨利 我了解你
Henry, I know you.
亨利 我对你了解很多
Henry, I know a lot about you.
我知道你在深海营救和逃生方面受过特训
I also know you are trained in deep sea rescue and retrieval.
你对我很有利用价值
Which makes you worth a lot to me.
如果你现在不帮我
Now, if you don't help me to get what I came for...
我会一个接一个杀死你家人
I will have to go after your family and kill them, one by one.
先从你儿子开始
And I will start with your son first.
亨利 请吧 最后的机会了
Henry, please, it's your final chance.
你沉默意思是你做出了错误的决定
I take it by your silence that you've made the wrong decision.
好了 该打猎了 出发
All right, it's time to hunt. Let's go.
我靠
Fuck me.
你！
You!
我以为你要护林员死
I thought you wanted the ranger dead.
我杀了他
I did.
改变了什么？
What changed?
我的主意
My mind.
救命
Fuck, help.
来吧！
Come on!
滚
Pass the fuck out!
来吧！
Come on!
滚开
Pass out! Pass the fuck out!
醒醒
Hey. Come on. Wake up.
你还不能死 死了我就没机会杀你了
You can't die yet. I won't get a chance to kill you.
那就太可惜了
Yeah, that'd be a shame.
看那家伙都怎么样了
Look what your friend dropped.
我有很多问题要问
Look, man, I've got a lot of questions to ask.
我有很多答案给你
Well, I've got answers.
甚至包括你没有想到的
Maybe even some you don't want.
因为我总是告诉你真相
But I'll always tell you the truth.
我们走吧
Let's get outta here.
我藏了个独木舟 以防你不喜欢游泳
I located a canoe in case you don't feel like swimming.
一报还一报
I'll do you one better.
不 不 不！
Aw, fuck. No, no, no!
护林员有没有被抓住？
Has the Ranger been captured, yes or no?
你们完蛋了
You're so fucked.
据我推测 你们最多还有三个人
By my count, that's three of you down so far.
滚开
Fuck off.
好了 我们走吧
Okay, let's go.
不 我们来探个究竟
No, no. We gotta see what's what.
- 你们还有多少人？  - 去死
- How many of you are left? - Eat a dick.
我当兵的时候
You know, when I was in the yard,
需要撬开某人的嘴时
when we wanted somebody to talk,
一般我们会挖掉一只眼睛
we'd carve one of the eyes out.
而且我注意到你有两只眼睛
Though I notice you've got two of 'em.
你不会的
You wouldn't.
- 给你三秒钟  - 求你阻止他！
- You've got three seconds. - You gotta stop him!
他听我的
Oh, yeah, he's really gonna listen to me.
- 一…  - 好吧！好吧
- One... - Okay! Okay, okay.
珊德 他叫珊德
Xander. His name is Xander.
他需要你潜水
He wants you to make a dive.
- 为了毒品  - 早说了是毒品
- For the drugs. - Told you it was drugs.
- 别吹牛  - 混蛋 你杀了我们的潜水员
- Don't brag. - You assholes, you killed our diver.
珊德知道你受过训练
Xander knew, he knew you were trained.
因为你杀了埃托
So when you killed Eto,
只能让你去潜水
we needed you to make the dive.
他怎么知道我能潜水？
How did he know that I could dive?
他知道很多
He knows things.
毒品在湖底？
The drugs are in the lake?
是大捆海洛因
It's a shipment of heroin.
在某个湖底
It went down in one of the lakes.
你们还有多少人？
How many of you are left?
- 就珊德  - 只有一个人？
- Just Xander. - Just one guy?
- 是啊  - 好 打昏他
- Yeah. - Good. Knock him out.
- 离开这鬼地方  - 走人
- Let's get the hell out of Dodge. - Let's go.
这么快就走了 泰勒先生？
Leaving so soon, Mister Taylor?
看过来
Over here.
事情其实很简单
I'll make this simple.
10分钟可赚50万
Half a million for ten minutes of work.
你的人都完了
You have no one left.
我们很清楚你只剩一个人
We know that you're the last one standing on your side of the equation.
最好的办法是回你的船
Your best bet is to get back on your boat
赶紧离开这里
and travel on out of here.
如果你现在离开 且不伤害别人
If you leave now without hurting anybody else,
我保证让警察处理你
I'll let the police handle you.
否则 我就亲自来找你
If you don't, I'll come for you myself.
相信我 你会更喜欢警察
Trust me, you'd prefer the police.
放马过来！ 我更喜欢和你斗 亨利
Bring that fire! I like this side of you, Henry.
我知道你想要什么 我不会为你潜水
I know what you want, and I'm not operating any dive.
你已经疯了
You've lost your mind.
今晚你将只剩一具躯壳
You've left nothing but bodies behind you tonight.
你听好了
Then you'll want to listen closely...
告诉你 我手里有你想要的人
when I tell you I have someone you want to keep safe.
这岛上还有其他人在？
There's somebody else on this island?
你发现的独木舟什么颜色？
What color was that canoe you found?
- 独木舟？  - 是啊 什么颜色？
- Canoe? - Yeah, what color was it?
银色和蓝色
Silver and blue.
是的 我有一个女人
Yes, I have a woman
她想跟你说话
who would like to speak to you.
亨利？
Henry?
凯拉？
Kayla?
约会你没露面 所以我来这里找你
You didn't show up for our date so I-I-I came out here.
这个人有枪 他有枪 亨利
This man's got a gun. He's got a gun, Henry.
真的 虽然我恨他们
It's true. Even though I hate them.
凯拉 坚持 我来救你
Kayla, hang on. I'm coming for you.
你做完我的工作
After you do your job,
就可以与年轻女士离开
you can leave with the young lady.
给你10分钟
You have ten minutes.
如果你不来…别怪我没提醒你
If you don't come... well, let's not talk about negatives.
你没有把握拿下这家伙
You're in no shape to take this guy.
跟在我后面过 但保持距离
Just come in after me, but keep your distance.
瞅准机会 赶紧走
If you see an opportunity to move in, take it.
请你千万盯着凯拉 懂吗？
Otherwise, keep your eyes on Kayla no matter what, okay?
算了吧 要我说 我们直接开船…
Forget that, man. I say we take this boat...
- 赶紧离开这个地狱  - 凯拉怎么办？
- and get the hell out of here. - What about Kayla?
是我的错 牵连她到这里
It's my fault that she's even here.
你不是说过不抛弃任何一个人吗
That's another person you wanna leave behind.
你忘记了吗？
What is it with you?
我去个这家伙交易
I just wanna make a trade with this guy.
希望他会放她走 你接走她
Hopefully he'll let her go, you get her,
尽一切可能离开这儿
you find anything that floats and you get outta here.
好吗？直到大陆 不要回头看
Okay? Straight to the mainland, don't look back.
找警察 告诉他们一切
Find the police, tell them everything.
不是一切
Well, not everything.
- 好 行动  - 这家伙会杀了你的
- Okay, go, come on. - This guy will kill you.
那我猜你应该感谢他
Well, I guess you should thank him.
祝你好运
Good luck.
这些作物在哥伦比亚是可以自由贸易的
You know, these beans are fair trade from Colombia.
不存在刀耕火种的农业
No slash-and-burn agriculture.
我敢肯定你完全不在乎(原始农业)
But you could care less, I'm sure.
她在哪里？
Where is she?
- 你朋友在哪里？  - 他离开了
- Where's your friend? - He left.
他坐凯拉的独木舟去求援
He took Kayla's canoe to get help.
届时一了百了 你彻底完蛋
But by the time he gets there, we'll be done and you'll be gone.
我倒是不怀疑
Why do I doubt that?
让我看凯拉 不然我走人
Show me Kayla or I turn around.
不错 但你忘了
Mmm, that's good. But you forget,
你不是发号施令的人
you're not the one who's calling the shots here.
你需要我去拿你想要的东西
You need me to get what you want.
你刚才的2小时就是很好的证明
You just spent the last two hours proving it.
没错 好的
Very true. Okay.
出来吧女孩
Outside, girl, now.
现在她来了
There she is.
让她先走
Let her go first.
我能威胁她 你也能说放她走
I can threaten her, you can say let her go,
你威胁我的时候 我可以把我的刀
you can threaten me, and I can put my, uh,
放在她喉咙上 这是一个循环
on her throat. It's all one big circle, you know.
我没有时间了
And I don't have the time.
她要么在这里等着 要么死
She waits here, or she die.
你只剩一人 还是按照我的方式去做吧
You're the only one left. We're gonna do this my way.
你输了 护林员 把枪放下
You lose, park ranger. Put the gun down.
很好
That's right.
下次你应该学会绑得紧一点
You know, you should learn to tie better knots... next time.
现在可以了吗？
Now then. Shall we?
上
Get on.
我去潜水 让她走
I'm making the dive. Let her go.
女孩留在这儿 你去干活
Or the girl stay here, you know, uh, you finish the job,
然后你们俩开船随便到天涯海角
and then both of you drive to the sunset.
如果他敢捣乱 仔细考虑我会对她怎么做
Let him think about what I'll do to her if he fucks with us.
弗朗索瓦 绅士点
Francois, be a gentleman.
呆着 我会带你离开这里 好吗？
Just hang in there. I'm gonna get you out of this, okay?
我哪儿也不去
I'm not going anywhere.
他答应了 来吧
He promise. Come on.
泰勒先生 我不是坏人
You know, Mister Taylor, I'm not a bad guy.
我和你一样服过兵役
I was in the service like yourself.
是吗？哪方面的？
Oh, yeah? Which side?
不很光彩的
That's not very nice.
现在你贩毒又杀人
Well, now you deal drugs and kill people.
相当的正确
It's so true.
我什么时候错过？
Where did I go wrong, huh?
我早该杀了你
I should've killed you when I had the chance.
- 你好么？  - 还好 这是怎么回事？
- You okay? - Yeah. What's going on here?
怎么回事？我们得离开这鬼地方
What's going on? We're getting the hell out of here.
我们不能就这样离开亨利
We can't just leave Henry.
亨利可以从容应对 相信我
Henry can handle himself, trust me.
那个男人会杀了他
That man will kill him.
他不会伤害他 因为他想要毒品
Look, he will not hurt him until he gets the drugs.
我们有时间去报告警察 然后回到这里
We've got time to go get the cops and get back here.
现在 我们走
Now let's go.
停下来
Stop.
举起你的双手
Put your hands up,
转身慢慢地面对我
turn around slowly and face me.
你在做什么？
What are you doing?
禁止警察 猎枪先生
No police, Mister Shotgun.
- 我操  - 我可不要
- Fuck me. - I'd rather not.
怎么样？
So how are we doing?
这衣服有点紧
The suit's a bit tight.
你的潜水员一定是矮子
He must've been kinda short, your diver.
不要侮辱埃托 时间在滴答
Don't insult Eto. Clock's ticking.
让你可以看清楚
So you can see.
- 谢谢  - 连接到包上 拉两次即可
- Thank you. - Attach this to the bag, tug twice.
必须在8分钟完成
You have eight minutes.
到第9分钟 你的女朋友会死的
In nine minutes, your lady friend will be dead.
好吗？别慢吞吞的
Okay? Don't be late.
在拉起之前 给我30秒钟清理通道
Just give me thirty seconds to clear out of the way before you pull it up.
泰勒 请小心
Oh, Mister Taylor. Be careful.
现在怎么办？
So what are we doing here?
闭嘴
Shut up.
我从你的眼睛看出你不是一个杀手
I can see it in your eyes, you're not a killer.
除了我的眼睛 你看不到我眼里有什么东西
You can't see shit in my eyes, except my eyes.
今晚对我们所有人来说都很艰难
Look, tonight's been hard on all of us,
珊德经常用我来分散别人注意力
except Xander quite often has me do a lot more to distract people.
屡试不爽
A lot more. So,
对你们来说很难理解 但我…
it may have been difficult for you people, except for me,
习以为常了
it's kind of been a breeze.
你只是个鸡？
So you're just a hooker?
我很受伤啊
I'm so hurt.
如果你要开枪
If you're gonna shoot me,
就开枪
shoot me.
好的
Okay.
妈的！
Shit!
你现在狼狈的很
I can tell you're in pretty rough shape.
为什么你不干脆出来 我们…
Why don't you just come on out and we'll...
我们彻底解决一下
And we'll work this out.
珊德 有快艇接近码头
Xander, a speedboat's approaching the dock.
有两名警察 我该怎么办？
It's two police officers. What should I do?
正常点 说你在钓鱼
Be normal. Tell them you're fishing.
同意支付罚款
Agree to pay the fine.
还有 速战速决
And, uh, be quick.
早上好 警官 我能为你做点什么？
Good morning, officers. What can I do for you?
今天早上你没见过的护林员 是吗？
You haven't seen the park ranger this morning, have you?
是的 几分钟前我刚上岛
No, I, uh, just got on the island a couple minutes ago.
一直在夜钓
Been doing some late night fishing.
现在是夜钓的季节吗？ 我不认为…
Is it season already? I don't think it's...
不 没关系 你抓到我了
Uh, no, okay, you caught me.
我总是一时头脑发热
I just, I always get a head start.
我愿意支付罚款
I'll pay the fine.
我们得到报告 说从岛上有巨响
Well, ma'am, we got a report of a loud noise coming from the island.
我们试图联系护林员 但无法联络…
We tried to reach the ranger, but couldn't get through so...
我不知道该怎么告诉你
I don't know what to tell you.
我还没有看到任何人呢
I haven't seen anybody yet.
射她！开枪！
Hey! Shoot her! Shoot her!
- 射她！  - 什么情况？
- Shoot her! - What the hell?
凯拉 去约定地点见我
Kayla, meet me at the pick-up site.
我已经拿到包裹
I've got the package.
镇静
Be convincing.
听起来不错 我照顾下我们的朋友
Sounds good. I took care of our friend.
我们离开这里
Let's get out of here.
很好
Very nice.
好 干的不错
Good, good work.
我还没说完呢
Oh, I'm not done yet.
这是一把ACR突击步枪
This is a Magpul ACR.
即便被水淹没几个小时后还能工作
It works after being submerged in water hours,
甚至几天数周
days, even weeks.
你厉害
You're great.
走
Come on. We're done here.
你去转动钥匙 把船开到岸边
You're gonna turn the key, drive to shore.
我去接凯拉 离开这里
I'm gonna get Kayla and we're getting outta here.
你再笑一笑 让你死
You look at me funny and you die.
你是老板
You're the boss.
提醒我一下 我们要干什么？
So remind me, what are we doing here?
警察来了
The cops are here.
交出毒品 你去坐牢
We're gonna hand over the drugs and you're going to jail.
明白？
You got it?
你指的是那些警察？
You mean those cops?
进去
All right, move it.
- 亨利！亨利！  - 嘿 闭嘴！
- Henry! Henry! - Hey, shut up!
- 感谢上帝 亨利  - 亨利
- Oh, thank God, Henry, - Henry.
你一定要帮我！他会杀了我！
you have to help me! He's gonna kill me!
她和他一伙的
She's with him.
- 不 亨利 我不是！  - 她是珊德的人
- No, Henry, I'm not! - She is with Xander.
继续前进
Keep moving.
Keep going.
克雷 你在做什么？
Clay, what are you doing?
他疯了！他会杀了我！
He's crazy! He's gonna kill me!
- 闭嘴！  - 你一定要帮我 亨利！
- Shut up! - You have to help me, Henry!
- 不要让他伤害我！  - 闭嘴！
- Don't let him hurt me! - Shut up!
- 他疯了…！  - 我不骗你
- He's crazy...! - I am not lying to you.
不要用枪指着我 伙计
Do not point that gun at me, man.
不要让他伤害我 亨利 求你了！
Don't let him hurt me, Henry, please!
听着 不要拿枪指着我
Listen, do not point that gun at me.
- 请 请  - 开枪打我
- Please. Please. - Point that gun at me.
- 听我说 好吗？  - 他疯了！
- Listen to me, okay? - He's crazy!
你要不要这个？
Hey! You want this? Huh?
你要不要这个？来吧！
You want this? Come on!
你搞砸了 宝贝 这不是很好
You fucked up, baby. That's not good.
亨利
Henry.
泰勒先生
You know, Mister Taylor,
大多数人从来不同时使用所有五个感官
most people never use all five senses at once.
而我？我会竭尽所能
Me? I use everything I've got.
因为我会比别人好 我的优势
That's why I'm better. That's my edge.
我们上树玩
We get to play in trees.
我来也 泰勒先生
I'm coming, Mister Taylor.
失败并不可耻
There's no shame in defeat.
睡吧 孩子
Sleep, my child.
开玩笑
You gotta be kidding me.
一个人应认识自己的局限性
A man has got to know his limitations.
好了 泰勒先生 你可以说“完了”
Well, Mr. Taylor, you can always say "almost."
再见 泰勒先生
Bye, Mister Taylor.
完了
Almost.
他妈的汽油
Fucking gasoline.
就知道这会毁了一切
I knew it would ruin everything.
起来
Come on.
谢谢
Thanks.
不许多嘴
Not a fucking word.
我闭嘴好了
Oh, my lips are sealed.